Freddy Roberts

CONTACT

2311 Riverside Drive, Nashville TN 37216

E-mail: me@freddyroberts.com **Website:** www.freddyroberts.com

Phone: (334)-479-2564

SKILLS

Languages: HTML, CSS, Javascript, PHP

CSS-Libraries: css-next, sass, bourbon/neat, bootstrap

Javascript-Libraries: ¡Query, react.js, vue.js

■ PHP-Libraries: Laravel, Wordpress

 Development Tools: Commandline/Terminal, Git, NPM, Gulp, Browserify, BrowserSync, Vagrant

ABOUT

I am pursuing a career in web development to engage my creative side, while also solving problems in a strategic way. Music and traveling are very strong passions of mine. While playing electric guitar for Hillsong Church, I had the opportunity to visit countries like England, Greece, Finland, Norway and Denmark. For the past 5 years I lived in Europe with my wife, who is Swedish. I love exploring different cultures, having lived on three continents has helped open my mind and given me a broader perspective on life.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Breakstation Creative

June 2016 — Present

Web Developer

We are building great products with great clients. Check out our work at http://www.brkstn.com/

DHL EXPRESS(Stockholm, SE)

2011 — 2015

Courier

- Time Management
- Route Planning
- Self Motivation

Hillsong Church(Sydney, AU)

2008 — 2010

Maintenance/Reception

- Team Work
- Service Focused Visitor Interactions
- Project Planning

DEV EXPERIENCE

Freelance Front end developer - Nashville, TN

- Hollymeyers.com A web portfolio, where I designed & developed from scratch using html, sass, jquery.
- Hinsonpoolcare.com A small business website designed & developed using react.js & sass.

The IRON YARD Front-End Engineering - Nashville, TN2015

A program facilitating projects, requirements, and teaching skills to junior developers.

55+hours a week building web applications, using HTML, CSS, Javascript

- Project Planning, both individually & with a team
- Worked on cross-platform projects with Ruby on Rails server-side engineers.
- Final project, Drobe, a web app built with react.js using Parse as an infrastructure

EDUCATION

Swedish A-D 2010 — 2011

SFI- Swedish for Immigrants

Stockholm, Sweden

Ministry & Leadership 2008 — 2009

Hillsong International Leadership College

Sydney, Australia

Freddy Roberts 2